{
    "id": "b57a3fe58127417d8db6d0347e540216",
    "title": "Finite And Non-finite Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My little brother 'wants' to be an actor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finite",
                "non-finite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3b71af2287ce44d88a6fbfb8582b7d6c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She worked hard 'to pass' the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finite",
                "non-finite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "698820bd44f14dd687685a521843a29b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I 'couldnâ€™t solve' the problem.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finite",
                "non-finite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1f9da1d8364447d49db02f88b32e5d0e"
        },
        {
            "question": "'To err' is human.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finite",
                "non-finite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1292aa91d7f44e0fbba4ece45c13f92f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your duty is 'to cross' the river without getting noticed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finite",
                "non-finite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6830267301fe4c9ea50ba605ca50a6b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor 'is attending' to the injured people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finite",
                "non-finite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bd29d8ecca7c4bf79395b284ec5cee6d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She 'opened' the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finite",
                "non-finite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9c36204578154f528b7a9320a17bf56a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The students were asked 'to submit' their assignments by Friday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finite",
                "non-finite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3ce818d63404448682f6a06a3abc12b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher 'encouraged' the students to work hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finite",
                "non-finite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "30b133aa0bdd4aae9414e36ab5073022"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog 'wagged' its tail to show its happiness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finite",
                "non-finite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0bb86b16d651404096b943db803bdabb"
        }
    ]
}